webssearches.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

EMG Technology Limited. ("Airzip") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about Airzip's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how Airzip receives, collects and uses information in connection with their website located at Airzip.com ("Site").Collection and Use of Information

##### Information You Provide:

When you register on the Site, you will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information, which may include your name, email address, age, gender, address, telephone number(s), areas of interest, login name, login password and other self-identifying information (all "Personal Information"). Airzip collects Personal Information primarily for the following purposes: (i) to maintain a record of registered users; (ii) to manage the login process and maintain users' personal preferences; (iii) to email registered users with news and updates; and (iv) to email promotional offers. In addition, Airzip may also collect information about you in surveys or for sweepstakes and contests on the Site and information about the searches you perform, promotional offers you choose and the pages you visit on the Site.

Airzip may also make certain message boards and forums available to you (collectively, "Forums"). You are solely responsible for the information andother content you post on and through these Forums and should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose Personal Information on or through these Forums, such information is generally accessible to and may be collected and used by other users. This Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. You are encouraged to exercise discretion when providing personal information about themselves in and through Forums. 

##### Information We Automatically Collect:

Airzip does not automatically collect any Personal Information on or through the Site, except as provided by you in connection with the registration process. Nevertheless, Airzip may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at Airzip's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. Airzip's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

Airzip may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. Airzip collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Airzip will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users. 

##### Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Airzip does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Airzip may disclose your Personal Information if Airzip believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Airzip; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Airzip (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Airzip services or members of the public.

Airzip may share aggregated demographic information about users with third party advertising and content companies. This information does not identify individual users and Airzip do not link aggregate user data with Personal Information. 

##### Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the Airzip website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

##### Security

Airzip takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although Airzip cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Airzip has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

##### Business Transitions

In the event that Airzip goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. Airzip will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information Airzip may have prior to such transfer.
